Hello
Hello everyone
Right now, it's heading to the University of Tokyo.
Is it possible?
From now on, we will meet our seniors, apparently about eight years ago.
It was decided that we would also give a presentation called the swing that was being done.
I'm still buying it
I will do my best
I want them to be independent and become idols.
On the other hand, I was auditioning.
Thank you for your presentation.
thank you
The result is a photo with no emotion.
Photos that embody vitality and vibrancy
I was able to take a photo of a person without weaknesses or flaws.
I think there is no correct answer depending on society.
That's something we can all do together.
I thought it would be better to learn such techniques when I was a student.
What started
Let's write something
When I look at Nagi in her usual clothes,
I thought you liked bright colors like red.
Nagi love cats.
She always say look at this cat, look at that cat.
She even showed us pictures of cats.
She has her own catchphrase
That's meow meow meow
Maybe I like cats too much myself.
It's like a special move combined with a cat.
The more I have it
But she also loves cats, so
I think each phrase really represents Nagi.
I'll give it to you a little later.
what do you say
thank you
That's amazing
Drawing out one's own knowledge
I think it's based on a movie
Among the topics
After all, I think She have a lot of knowledge about painting.
I like the person himself and feel like it adds to her personality.
Really, what is it, young lady?
There is that, but the wording etc.
I often wish I knew every single detail.
Really, young lady, what is it?
50 years old?
But it's a lot of action, and it's a lot of pocket money.
I think I often feel that way.
Hey
really from morning till night
There are times when we don't talk.
I've been talking for as long as I thought
There are also stories about her riding her bicycle to various places.
surely
It's just a guess, but I think it's her personal boom.
That's correct.
My boom is why I'm going for a walk.
Okay, a walk.
Hot paper is quite difficult.
It's an instruction, but I wonder if it makes sense.
There are many things.
idol ideas
I think they want idols to be independent. I do this because an adult told me to.
Last time, our seniors had a handshake event that was very powerful because they had a real experience that was unique to them. So, I think it would be better for us to include experiences that only we experience. hand.
Isn't the target audience listening to this probably college students? People who are about to get a job. So, when we get a job, from the perspective of those people, we've already finished getting a job.
He's a job hunter.
surely.
I think it would be a good idea to bring up the story of the audition as a theme. I think it's really cool.
I think that's what the other side wants to hear. It certainly seems like it will become a characteristic of Nagezaka.
It seems to be connected to something like that.
However, there is still a question and voting function. Voting function. Ah, but when it comes to voting, I guess there are two or three choices.
No, ○×.
Doing assignments with everyone, sharing them, etc.
I have to put together what came out of that.
Is there an investment in the audition?
Reports and greetings when you are cornered
I feel like I'm being watched a lot even when I'm not interviewing.
We also learned about it for the first time here.
I felt like I wanted to know first, and when I realized that I was taking it easy,
People looking for jobs too
I wonder if that's the case, I wish I knew sooner.
I feel at ease and can face job hunting.
I thought something like that might happen.
On the other hand, I was auditioning.
I think this child is extremely loved.
The kids who I understood are now doing things with me at the same time.
When I became an idol, I was very conscious of my weaknesses in things like arms and dancing.
There is some cause for concern though.
Is there a positive strength that outweighs that?
I looked at the sky and
He was definitely someone who should be let down.
Why did you choose it?
Just look for a reason
I think that will be my strength
I have been walking for 3 years
If you can show me how you're obsessed and not
I heard that this might be a hint of centrality.
That seems to be a bit of a hint for the brand.
I have no recollection of that.
thank you for your hard work
There are many people who like me too.
It's like trying out an interview in person.
I think there is one thing.
On the set or conversely, on the interviewer side too.
Will you make a big mess?
Will it put a lot of pressure on me?
thank you
Do you think idols are human-like?
So that's it
We at Nogizaka46 have come to think about what it means to be human.
I started thinking about whether the idol group Nogizaka46 is human-like.
To all those who wish to withhold themselves from us.
We will propose a new grand
Students in the Department of Language and Expression, Faculty of Letters, etc.
I decided to recommend it because of the meaning of human small fry.
Looks like a swing
I've been facing my own personality
There was no time to not think about the swing.
I was always thinking
It's okay, because when we stand on stage, we're idols.
If we were idols, if we were idols
It's okay, you can do it. I can do anything. Let's all support each other. Are you okay. Ask for help if something happens Please take a look.
Well then, let's go. Let's do our best. I'm going. Seino, Seino, Seino, gratitude, smile , backwards, that's right, that's right, body six.
My own thoughts
Thank you for your hard work
So everyone, thank you for your presentation.
thank you
From everyone's perspective
objectively
Idols are perfect idols
People who have an image
I think there are many
Personally I thought
Is it actually true?
Become a member of Nogizaka46
I asked
using the survey form
I asked two questions
From these answers
What is humanity?
Suddenly, I see myself as I am.
I think it's time to show it to you.
we think
we are like you too
I think so
I'm worried about the switching and balance between my true self and my version of myself.
I found out that it was confusing
After receiving this input, we thought about what we wanted to do and what we should do.
That's it here
Accept both your true self and the versioned version of yourself.
I wanted to create a brand that would make people fall in love with themselves.
About the form of output we considered
What we thought was NOGI diagnosis
This is commonly known as Nogi diagnosis.
Nogi diagnosis is about knowing who you are and who you have made up.
It's a service that you can like no matter who you are.
Please answer the questionnaire as shown here
On top of that, here I will be speaking from the standpoint of both my true self and my versioned self.
I'll ask you to answer
This is an image of the result
In Nogi diagnosis
Something like this
You can also see the results of his death compared to the members of Nogizaka46. What we really want to convey through this brand is
We want to affirm your humanity, whether you're as you are or how you've made things up. And you like that
I love you
thank you for your hard work
thank you
you were good
we were kind
Everyone, look at the kid with the washing machine.
what are you doing
yes!
it's over
good job
I can't see the goal so much that I wonder if I'll actually get to the point where I'll give you a present in 2 months.
I couldn't see the future, so I was really worried.
When I finished it, it was so rewarding.
I feel like there is no other job that is so fun.
I think it was a really valuable experience.
When everyone gets on stage again
I think it will change
I agree
The degree of completion of the presentation towards the end
It was impressive that it went up so much.
I really think about it every day
I agree
It wasn't the day I was thinking about it.
It's amazing that it's over
It's also lonely
But I think it was a wonderful experience.
Because it's a first year student
I think there was so much to be gained.
3,000th
It was fun everyone
thank you for your hard work
Please subscribe to the channel and give us a high rating.
Please also like
thank you